[{"question":"# Q1. How can you increase the CPU resources for your Lambda?","options":["Increase the configured CPU value","Increase the configured timeout value","Increase the configured memory value","Increase the configured concurrency value"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Increase the configured memory value"},{"question":"# Q2. How can additional code or content can be provided for Lambda?","options":["blocks","layers","aliases","handlers"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"layers"},{"question":"# Q3. How can Step Functions call Lambdas?","options":["in sequence","both of these answers","neither of these answers","in parallel"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"both of these answers"},{"question":"# Q4. Which AWS CLI command invokes a function?","options":["aws lambda invoke --function ReturnBucketName outputfile.txt","aws lambda execute --function-name ReturnBucketName outputfile.txt","aws lambda invoke --function-name ReturnBucketName outputfile.txt","aws lambda execute --function ReturnBucketName outputfile.txt"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"aws lambda invoke --function-name ReturnBucketName outputfile.txt"},{"question":"# Q5. What adds tracing capabilities to a Lambda?","options":["AWS Trace","CloudStack","CloudTrail","AWS X-Ray"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"AWS X-Ray"},{"question":"# Q6. You need to build a continuous integration/deployment pipeline for a set of Lambdas. What should you do?","options":["Create configuration files and deploy them using AWS CodePipeline.","Create CloudFormation templates and deploy them using AWS CodeBuild","Create configuration file and deploy using AWS CodeBuild","Create CloudFormation templates and deploy them using AWS CodePipeline."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Create CloudFormation templates and deploy them using AWS CodePipeline."},{"question":"# Q7. What can you use to monitor function invocations?","options":["API Gateway","S3","SAS","CLoudTrail"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"CLoudTrail"},{"question":"# Q8. It is AWS best practice to enable Lambda logging by which of these methods.","options":["Use S3 metrics and CloudWatch alarms","Create custom metrics within your Lambda code.","Create custom metrics within your CloudWatch code.","Use Lambda metrics and CloudWatch alarms."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Use Lambda metrics and CloudWatch alarms."},{"question":"# Q9. What may be provided for environment variables?","options":["an SSL certificate","a bitmask","an AWS KMS key","an HTTP protocol "],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"an AWS KMS key"},{"question":"# Q10. Lambda allows for running of what other things?","options":["binaries.","all of these answers","executables","Shell scripts"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"all of these answers"},{"question":"# Q11. In what style must you write Lambda code?","options":["MVC","virtual","stateless","protocol"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"stateless"},{"question":"# Q12. How can a developer provide Lambda code?","options":["by uploading a .zip file","all of these answers","by editing inline","from an S3 bucket"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"all of these answers"},{"question":"# Q13. You are performance-testing your Lambda to verify that you set the memory size adequately. Where do you verify the exectuon overhead?","options":["CLoudWatch logs","DynamoDB logs","S3 logs","Lambda logs."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Lambda logs."},{"question":"# Q14. What facilitates continuous delivery of Lambdas?","options":["CodeStack","ElasticStack","Mobile Hub","CodeDeploy"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"CodeDeploy"},{"question":"# Q15. How are computing resources allocated to Lambdas?","options":["proportionally","equally","periodically","daily"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"proportionally"},{"question":"# Q16. You can restrict the scope of a user's permissions by specifying which two items in an IAM policy?","options":["resources and users","resources and conditions","events and users","events and conditions"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"resources and conditions"},{"question":"# Q17. What does Lambda logging include?","options":["logging streams","rotating streams","logging events","advancing log groups"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"logging streams"},{"question":"# Q18. What can AWS Amplify NOT do for a Lambda?","options":["create a Lambda","be an event source","assign an IAM role","delete a Lambda"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"be an event source"},{"question":"# Q19. How do you author a Lambda in a programming language that AWS does not support?","options":["Create a Lambda function with a custom runtime and reference the function in your Lambda","Create a Lambda layer with a custom runtime and reference the layer in your lambda","You cannot use Lambda in this situation","Create a Lambda function with a custom runtime"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Create a Lambda layer with a custom runtime and reference the layer in your lambda"},{"question":"# Q20. What are listed downstream resources based on?","options":["the execution policy","the Lambda configuration","the Lambda nodes","the IAM user"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"the Lambda configuration"},{"question":"# Q21. Which is an equivalent and valid tag for a pair of Lambdas?","options":["department:Sales,department:Sales","department:Sales,department:sales","aws:demo;aws:demo","aws:demo;aws:DEMO"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"department:Sales,department:sales"},{"question":"# Q22. Outbound connections from Lambdas must be `**\\_\\_**`.","options":["neither of these answers","UDP/IP","TCP/IP","both of these answers"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"both of these answers"},{"question":"# Q23. How are CloudWatch actions configured?","options":["automatically","none of these answers","manually","ad hoc"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"manually"},{"question":"# Q24. You are testing your stream-based application and the associated Lambda. AWS best practice advises you to test by varying what?","options":["stream and record sizes","stream and shard sizes","batch and record sizes","batch and shard sizes"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"batch and record sizes"},{"question":"# Q25. You need to make your Lambda available to services in multiple VPCs. What do you do?","options":["Place each subnet in a VPC. Associate all subnets to your Lambda.","Place all subnets in a VPC. Associate all subnets to your Lambda.","Configure your Lambda to be available to multiple VPCs.","Configure all application VPCs to be peered."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Configure all application VPCs to be peered."},{"question":"# Q26. How is the cost associated with Lambda function calculated?","options":["number of function calls","amount of code run","compute time","amount of infrastructure used"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"compute time"},{"question":"# Q27. What is the fastest way to get started with Lambda?","options":["Author a Lambda from scratch.","Use a blueprint.","Use a .zip deployment package.","Use the serverless app repository."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Use a blueprint."},{"question":"# Q28. Where is the disk space allocated for Lambda functions?","options":["/tmp","/default","/temp","/ds"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"/tmp"},{"question":"# Q29. How do you stop a running Lambda that is stuck in a recursive loop?","options":["Delete the function.","Set the function concurrent execution limit to 0 while you update the code.","Reset the function.","Set the function concurrent execution limit to 100 while you update the code."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Set the function concurrent execution limit to 0 while you update the code."},{"question":"# Q30. What is AWS best practice for Lambda configuration?","options":["Overprovision memory to run your functions faster and reduce your costs. Do not overprovision your function timeout settings.","Overprovision memory and your function timeout settings to run your functions faster and reduce your costs.","Do not overprovision memory. Overprovision your function timeout settings to run your functions faster and reduce costs.","Do not overprovision memory. Do not overprovision your function timeout settings to run your functions faster and reduce costs."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Overprovision memory to run your functions faster and reduce your costs. Do not overprovision your function timeout settings."},{"question":"# Q31. Basic Lambda permissions include permissions for what?","options":["removing log groups","none of these answers","creating log groups","updating log groups"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"updating log groups"},{"question":"# Q32. How are environment variables stored?","options":["DynamoDB tables","key-value pairs","S3 buckets","none of these answers"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"key-value pairs"},{"question":"# Q33. You need to use a Lambda to provide backend logic to your website. Which service do you use to make your Lambda available to your website?","options":["S3","API Gateway","X-Ray","DynamoDB"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"API Gateway"},{"question":"# Q34. How can additional code or content be provided for your Lambda?","options":["aliases","blocks","handlers","layers"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"layers"},{"question":"# Q35. Lambdas allow for running of what other things?","options":["binaries","executables","all of these answers","shell scripts"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"all of these answers"},{"question":"# Q37. You are creating a Lambda to trigger on change to files in an S3 bucket. Where should you put the bucket name?","options":["in the Lambda function code","in a Lambda environment variable","in the Lambda tags","in another S3 bucket"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"in a Lambda environment variable"},{"question":"# Q38. What action is needed before you can test a Lambda?","options":["Deploy the Lambda.","Export the function","none of these answers","Configure a test event."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Configure a test event."},{"question":"# Q39. What kind of packages can you use with Node.js for Lambdas?","options":["Fleece","NPM","none of these answers","Pod"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"NPM"},{"question":"# Q41. Lambdas are monitored by default using which service?","options":["CloudTrail","CloudWatch","CloudFormation","LogWatch"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"CloudWatch"},{"question":"# Q42. What can trigger a Lambda function execution?","options":["a table definition","queue isolation","STS Write","an SNS topic"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"an SNS topic"},{"question":"# Q43. You need to set an S3 event trigger on your Lambda to respond when data is added to your bucket from another S3 bucket. Which event type do you configure?","options":["POST","\"All object create events\"","PUT","COPY"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"PUT"},{"question":"# Q44. To make Lambdas more testable, it is AWS best practice to separate which of these?","options":["Lambda configuration from logging code","Lambda handler from logging code","Lambda handler from core logic","Lambda configuration from core logic"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Lambda handler from core logic"}]